[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1 / 1",
        "answers": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "2 / 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "3 / 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "4 / 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "5 / 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "1 / 2",
        "answers": [
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1,
            1.25
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "2 / 2",
        "answers": [
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1,
            1.25
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "3 / 2",
        "answers": [
            0.5,
            0.85,
            1.15,
            1.5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1.5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "4 / 2",
        "answers": [
            1,
            1.5,
            2,
            2.5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "5 / 2",
        "answers": [
            1.5,
            2,
            2.25,
            2.5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2.5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "1 / 3",
        "answers": [
            0.33,
            0.67,
            1,
            1.33
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.33,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "2 / 3",
        "answers": [
            0.33,
            0.67,
            1,
            1.33
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.67,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "3 / 3",
        "answers": [
            0.33,
            0.67,
            1,
            1.33
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "4 / 3",
        "answers": [
            0.33,
            0.67,
            1,
            1.33
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1.33,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "5 / 3",
        "answers": [
            0.67,
            1,
            1.33,
            1.67
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1.67,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "1 / 4",
        "answers": [
            0.25,
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.25,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "2 / 4",
        "answers": [
            0.25,
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "3 / 4",
        "answers": [
            0.25,
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0.75,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "4 / 4",
        "answers": [
            0.25,
            0.5,
            0.75,
            1
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "5 / 4",
        "answers": [
            0.75,
            1,
            1.25,
            1.5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1.25,
        "clicked": false
    }
]